sound of 'Aye Aah' is also heard.
[Music]
Come on Nawab Saheb, dance with us.
Excuse me, why are you calling my brother-in-law Nawab
?  District, we are
handicapped because of our manners.  If we make them then what all do we
call them, oh
my heart was alone you played such a game
in your memory [music]
I am like a magician [music] [music
]
[music]
what's the matter what's the matter oy hoye hoye hoye
[encouraging voice]
Archana ji
yes ji
look at the dazzling
Subhan Allah of the neighborhood
your Chandu has done it ok
yes ji the
child is not Yadav yes yes it is
his child's birthday today
oh
yes ji he has two twins three Tadwa and one
bitter
one minute what is this bitter friend the one that
bites
and his wife Titli Yadav she says
on the child's birthday no Qawwali night queen.
Well,
a scheme came to my mind.
Yes.
Kappu will become Kawal and we will loot Bachcha
Jadhav's property.  [cheering]
[applause]
But there's one condition.  You should not tell anyone.
No, dear.
Hey, you don't understand, friend.   It will not happen at all.   Oh, it wo
n't happen.  [MUSIC]
Oh no no.
[Encouraging voice]
Oh no, man.
Oh wow.
Look friend, these arrangements are fine but
Archana ji, you tell me
who organizes a Qawwali on the birthday of a small child, it will be
Qawwali, it will be Qawwali,
hey, let's organize a DJ night, friend, let's keep doing Tamma Tamma,
in the name of Tamma Tamma Tamma Tamma, I have become the mother of 12 children,
friend, look at the child, I have made complete
preparations for the birthday.  Now you quickly order a six-storey
cake.  You have to commit suicide by jumping from that six-storey building.   The
street vendor wants a six-story cake.  Now
if the big Kawal does not come then we will
put your face in the middle of your Kawal's claps.  Then the fuchak fuchak
fuchak fuchak sound will continue.
[cheering]
[applause]
Look, Bacha.  You are taking such tension.  Such
Qawwals will come and sing such Qawwalis.   Do
you know that your children will
sing Qawwalis and not lullabies?   Are
?  Will you listen to Qawwali instead of lullaby?  Did
you turn your grandmothers and great-grandmothers into fools by feeding them paan
?
You just see it now.  So please welcome me with loud applause.
Qawwal, Ustadji,
[screaming sound]
Khan Sahib.
[cheering sound]
[music] I
think about how innocent they were.
[MUSIC]
[Cheers] I
think about how innocent they were.
[Encouraging voice]
[Music]
[Encouraging voice] I
think,
Ustad ji, what is the matter, I
think, you will think, I think,
how innocent he was, what he became after
seeing him [Music] He
knew how much he became after seeing him [Music]
Look, how well
he knew [Music] what he became, see, what a
wonderful thing has been said, well, what a wonderful
thing,
who has
said so beautifully for Archana ji, she used to
come from the jetty after wooing the jetty man, wow wow, she used to
come from the jetty after wooing the jetty man, now she
comes directly in an auto after giving him the fare
and what does the jetty man say after seeing her in the auto
?  What happened, look [music]
What's the matter, Ustad ji, what's the matter, ah
yes, it's your child's birthday, Jile Lal,
where do I have to perform the Qawali, I have to perform it on the moon, oh, this is what I will do, friend,
look, I have decorated it so much, O Lord, this is what I have to perform the
Qawali, has
any old poet said
that a bird sleeps on every branch, do
n't listen to such a big thing.   A
bird sleeps on every branch.
Even the wedding night room is decorated.
If you sing the same Qawwali then when will
you celebrate your wedding night?
Very good.
And if we don't celebrate our wedding night,
where will the children come from?  [laughter]
And if the children don't come, then the relatives will
sing the same song, look what has happened [music]
how are you
[music]
wow wow Ustad ji, it was fun, what is your name
[laughter]
My name is Ustad Medium Begum Ali Khan Sahib,
medium,
look, it is a male type
name, then why is it a female type name, let me
tell you, actually he
likes Badshah very much and when he
sees Badshah, the Begum inside him comes out.
He said it right Your Majesty,
come and take my life [laughs] I do
n't like your behaviour,
what kind of things do you say, your dhoti is so thin
dear, what happened in the blink of an eye, friend, what happened in the blink of an eye,
you had said that she is very famous,
I have never heard the name Begum Ali Khan.
So how would you have heard it?  Earlier he was famous by the name of Hansraj Hans.
Who is this?   Is it
Hansraj Hans?  No. No.  His
face does not match theirs.
That's why we have become Daler Mehndi.
We know him too, he has come here.
Makeup has
also arrived.
Guru Randhawa has
Oh God.  All Punjabis come here.   Do you
give me a Canadian visa?
Look, if you are not any of these then
how did you become famous?  We used to be Neha Kakkar earlier.
She is a lady.   I
told you that the Begum inside them wakes up, so
that day Neha Kakkar went there.
Then why should I not knock the door Raja Sitao hoye hoye raja oe hoye hoye raja oe hoye hoye raja hoye raja [
music] Ovi
why are you dancing your husband is standing here you are
calling the king that too without knocking the door at least get the
door knocked [laughter]
Tataluk na kare nava
we will sing such songs for you that you will embrace us without Eid.
First tell me the truth, have you ever done any Qawwali with anyone else
?   I have done this
many times, but Nawab Saheb has never been caught.   Was
not caught.  [laughter] Did
n't get caught.
Yes sir.  They do Qawwali by running around like this.  Do
n't get caught.   Oh,
your kurta is so thin.
How did it happen in the blink of an eye?
[Music]
Look, I am sensing something fishy,
otherwise why are you not telling me
with whom you have sung the Qawali, Didi,
why are you talking like this, Moti Apa,
we have a very famous Qawali,
you might have heard of it,
which one?
These black Qawali eyes [Music]
These fair gore cheeks,
these black black eyes [Music] Fair
gore ga
[Music]
This seems to be heard of, no no, there is nothing like that,
Ustad ji has
also sung Qawali with Michael Jackson,
yes, when did Michael Jackson sing Qawali,
actually Michael Jackson sahab
tried Qawali from there, tell me what is it,
he did not do it, we
started Qawali, he started walking in such a way that we cannot do it, he is
not walking like this, that is moon walk, it is
his famous step, we still
cannot believe it.  This is some Qawwal, Chandu.
What are you saying Jile Lahi?  Ca
n't you see this flexibility of the waist?
Jile Ilahi,
if you permit me, I will start the Qawwali.   Wait
a minute, Ustad ji, if you are in the mood for wet Qawwali, should
I get a diaper from inside
?  [Music]
This is the hook step of our Qawwali, Motipa.
You won't understand.
Didi
Jiju [music]
Puri
Come on come on
Didi first take the gift
Gift [laughs]
How cute my sister is, what a
gift she has brought, let me see I
think they open a new gift in front of everyone, they do
n't open it for us.  You are from the house.
You are right.
Look at this.
Savings kit?
You bring a savings kit for our one year old child.
Yes brother-in-law, you yourself say that nowadays
children grow up before their age.  Now
who knows, your child may also grow a beard in a month or two.
Dude, this girl has
n't gained any sense in all these years.  A small child
grows a beard.  Yes, this is your absolutely rubbish gift.
Hey sister, I myself am the gift.
Today I will perform magic on your child's birthday.
Your magic has already taken over me.
[Encouraging voice]
What's on your mind isn't magic.
This is okay.
And sister, why have you invited this inauspicious person on such an auspicious occasion
?
Called means I have organised this entire party.
What?
Yes.  And
I have brought all the Qawwali masters here.
These people and other masters
sell powder in buses.
These and other
such people buy powder from the same buses and
consume it.   The
sound of sigh is also heard.
[Music]
Come on Nawab Saheb, let's dance with us.
Excuse me, why are you calling my brother-in-law Nawab
?
District, we are handicapped because of our manners.
Otherwise, what do we call them?   Yes,
my heart was alone, you played like this in your
memories [Music],
I played magic all night long [Music]
Magic
[Music]
What's the matter, what's the matter,
Sapna, are you crazy,
today is not my friend's wedding, today is my children's
birthday, no, no, it was
my friend's wedding, I
could not go there, so I thought my dance would be
wasted, so I came here and did
this, anyway,
happy birthday,
happy birthday.
Happy birthday is fine.  Why have you
brought the cylinder with you?
Hey, this is a gift for your child.
Cylinder
yes
shaving kit.  It's our child's birthday.   There has
not been a flood yet and all the relief funds are coming here too.   Do
n't mind, I will come to the district.   She is a
woman like a gas plant.  She will only gift the cylinder,
what else can she do?
I said something.  I said something.
I am the child's aunt.  Aunty,
well, this guy too has his own thing going on
here.  [laughs]
Wherever she sees her own benefit, she makes a relationship.
Sometimes she becomes someone's nephew.
Sometimes she becomes someone's aunt.  Sometimes she becomes someone's
sister.  It is made.
I would still have made relationships.  Not like you.
His family members reject him.
His own father goes out
with him, right?  He says he is my aunt's son.
Oh, the woman bigger than the JCB machine,
I am a JCB, I am very good, I am telling you that I will bury
you even after digging at your place, I am
telling you, I am Titli Bhabhi, tell these people,
I am the child's aunt,
hello, there are no
wells of death like yours,
not an aunt, I am the
original aunt,
see, you are like a candle, if you blow on it, it will
extinguish, the elder one is here,
beware, if I trouble you like this on my child's birthday,
hey Kapal sahab, what are you doing, you have come to see the fight between women, oh, it is a
lot of fun to see the fight between women, in
our place, if there is no fight, then I will make these
two girls fight among themselves, Juda
beating is very famous in our place,
Jilelahi
Ustad ji, you start the Qawwali.
Why does Moti Apa get angry?
Let's start the Qawwali.
Yes, do it.
Come and sit next to us and
enjoy the quality.  [laughter]
[music]
Yeah, let's get started.
So let us start this colourful birthday evening
with his name.
Who is the head of this locality.  Yes, okay, okay,
what's the matter, I have
requested
[Music]
People came
here to
earn money,
somehow or the other,
people ate Siddh's chair,
how
[Music]
[Music] She
eats it at one time.  Eats one at a time
[music].  She also takes the bag home in polythene.  It
also takes the house [music].   She
laughs so loudly.  Even the witch gets scared.  She gets
scared [music].  By becoming Kapoor Bhai, she
also makes people laugh.  It also takes away.   The one who
causes trouble [music]
You will regret the heart [music] The
day he comes he will take him away The
day he comes [music] he will
take away
[music] he will take away
[voice of song] he will take away
[music] he will take away So
ladies and gentlemen, I have made a request for Bachcha Yadav
whose son's birthday is at
11 o'clock I don't know what he eats, let's go for a
walk for two minutes [music] he becomes a child, he becomes a
child he becomes a child he looks
like a watermelon how is his hairstyle,
understand the heart, he looks like a hero, he looks exactly like [music] he is like this, exactly like this, exactly like this
how long will he keep telling jokes on elders
[music] but because of this elders will get banned
[music] he will
take away he will take away he will take away
take away wow wow wow
this is very good
what a thing Ustad ji what a thing it is,
now you have heard it on us, so now play a little on
our behalf, on our wife, on the
butterfly, take it on our
behalf, take it, take it for whatever
work it is for them  I have come here with the money and have
requested for the fat one, so what is
your beauty?
Its name is butterfly.  It looks good but it eats.   She
eats 100 rotis in one sitting [music].
She eats while sitting.  She eats while sitting.   The
kids say it's Mummy [music]
Parila.  Consider yourself Munni who looks like
Akila [music].   It
is a fair.  No matter how much you try [music], no matter how much
you do [music], it won't be possible, the
dung
eater will eat so much food,
so much food [music] will eat, will eat
[music] will
eat, will
eat
Now let's talk about the grasshopper which is smaller than the butterfly.
Bolo
distributes equal cards in gambling [music].  She
picks your pocket in two minutes in the train.  She
takes the bite [music].  She bites it.
Chandu Bhave wala loves this one a lot [music].
Open your mouth and see, there is two and a half grams of gold.   She goes
here and there and gives auditions [music] and
pulls the goat by tying it to a boat.  She pulls
[music] The goat pulls.  Those who die in this
[music] tomorrow, those who
die in this tomorrow, you will regret it a lot.
[Music] You will also marry her.  The fleet will be wrong.
You will also marry her.  My
[music] It will be my home It will be
my home It will be my home It will be my home It will be my home It will be my home It will be my home
I am ready to turn the tables Come on
[laughs]
Oh Sapnooli You are laughing a lot, aren't you
Ustad ji, tell me something about this Sapnooli
Oh no, tell me, she was laughing a lot during our time too
Take this and tell me, you
count this Ustad with this Is she fake, what a request she has made
What a thing She
applies hot oil on her body [song voice] She bathes the notes in the parlor Under these pretexts She
bathes the notes [music] She bathes the notes
In a 10-minute entry She dances for seven minutes
from the actors again and again [music] She asks for one crore She asks for
one crore Those who roam around disguised as girls
[music] Those who
roam around disguised as girls Will not be able to become a boy Until then
Govinda will eat
[screaming sound]
[music] Till then Govinda will eat
[music]
Mama will
eat I really enjoyed the preparations you made I
really enjoyed it deep inside I just did
n't  Please say a little about him too,
I want some spit to come out of his ears too
[laughs]
Brother, take whatever is left of mine too,
but tell me, oh
Allah, the entire bank has come, I have made a throne for this Chandu,
Ustad ji, please reduce it a little,
I am not Chandu that I will reduce it.   I will do whatever I have
promised to Soni sir.
[Music]
His name is Chandu.  It is found on the road.
He earns money in the name of God [music].
He earns and eats.  He earns and eats.
He snatches biscuits from the mouth [music].  Nothing
else comes without Oye Oye.
And [music] nothing comes.  Nothing else comes to mind.
In the affair of friendship [music] In the
affair of friendship [music] How long will it take to fall asleep
?  Make some arrangement of your own, you will die of hunger.
Make some arrangement for yourself, you will
die hungry [music].  Make some arrangement for yourself,
you will die of hunger.  Make some arrangement for yourself
[music]
You will die of hunger.  You will die of hunger.
You will die of hunger.  I will die, I will die [music] I will die, I will die
[music] I will die, I will die, I will die [music] Let
the alap be completed quickly, alap live for
one minute, one minute, you do
n't want to
take it
[music]
[praise]
Sharma
Pappu Sharma Sharmapurma
one second one second, girls, girls, you all
leave.  Take an auto and tell him to keep it started.
Hurry up, hey, take the money too.
Firstly, God knows why we get caught in the end.
My salwar is getting
loose due to fear.  Wait a second, two minutes.
We have to rob.   The
place of singing is sacred.  Don't wear shoes.   He is
preparing.
What was the need to take up the job?
[music]
Jay